tradingcentral.com 2013-10-08

# TRADING Central - TECHNICAL ANALYSIS EXPERTS

**Privacy Statement of TRADING CENTRAL SA**

## Information about our Organisation and Web site

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organisation like TRADING CENTRAL SA . We are based in FRANCE . 

Our principal activity is: Financial Research 

Our privacy policy covers TRADING CENTRAL SA and its Web sites: 

| Organisation Name: | TRADING CENTRAL SA  
---|---  
Address: | 11 BIS RUE SCRIBE  
City, Zip: | PARIS,75009  
Country: | FRANCE  
Controller: | CNIL  
Web Sites(s): | www.tradingcentral.com  
www.charts.fr  
www.lobsa.com  
  
Our privacy policy also covers our subsidiaries and their respective Web sites: 

Subsidiary Name: | TRADING CENTRAL AMERICAS, INC  
---|---  
Address: | 60 BROAD STREET  
City, Zip: | NEW YORK , 10004  
State | NY  
Country: | USA  
Controller: | TRADING CENTRAL SA  
Principal activity(ies): | Financial Research  
Web Sites(s): | www.tradingcentral.com  
  
Subsidiary Name: | TRADING CENTRAL ASIA LIMITED  
---|---  
Address: | 1301 BANK OF AMERICA TOWER 12 HARCOURT ROAD  
City, Zip: | HONG KONG , CENTRAL  
Country: | HONG KONG  
Controller: | TRADING CENTRAL SA  
Principal activity(ies): | Financial Research  
Web Sites(s): | www.tradingcentral.com  

## Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access

You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data. 

## The services and links of our Web sites

Our Web sites do not enable our visitors to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. 

Our Web sites may include links to third party Web service providers. 

## Automatic Collection of Information

We automatically log personal data by means such as programming or we link information automatically logged by such means with personal data about specific individuals. We do so for the following purposes: 

  * Customer administration

We do not use cookies to store personal data. 

## Data Collection and Purpose Specification

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please click here

We do not collect or use personal data for any purpose other than that indicated in the table below. 

If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we offer you the means to consent to this new purpose: by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected 

## Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We do not take specific steps to protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us. 

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data. 

## Disclosure and Visitor Choice

We disclose our visitors' personal data to our subsidiaries or other organisations. 

Where we disclose your personal data for the same purposes as those indicated in the table below, we provide you with the means to opt-in to disclosure: 

  * by indicating in a box at the point on the site where personal data is collected

Where we disclose your personal data for purposes which are different from those indicated in the table mentioned below, we do not offer you the opportunity to consent to disclosure. 

## Confidentiality / Security

We give you the option of using a secure transmission method to send us the following types of personal data: 

  * primary personal data (such as name and contact details)

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorised access
  * improper use or disclosure
  * unauthorised modification
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

## Access to the personal data we may hold about you

You can ask us by sending an email whether we are keeping personal data about you. 

Upon request, which you can indicate by: 

  * sending postal mail to this address: TRADING CENTRAL 11 BIS RUE SCRIBE F-75009 PARIS

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month. - although we may before require proof of your identity -. We will provide the information without any charge. 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * erased
  * rectified or amended
  * completed

We do not reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. 

## Privacy Compliance

Our privacy policy is compliant with the following authority: CNIL, FRANCE ([www.cnil.fr](http://www.cnil.fr/english)) 

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organisation. 

In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above authority, we are: 

  * voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure

#### Self Assessment procedure

Name or designation of the privacy policy person or service | TRADING CENTRAL SA  
---|---  
URL | www.tradingcentral.com  
Address | 11 BIS RUE SCRIBE F-75009 PARIS  
Country | FRANCE  

**TABLE of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used**

#### Primary personal data/Business information

**x** | volunteered by each visitor  
---|---  
- | collected from public records or bodies  
**-** | collected from private organisations  
  
Primary personal data | Technical administration of the Web site | Research & development | Customer Administration | Marketing | Trading in personal data  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Name | **x** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **x**  
Gender | **-** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **x**  
Address | **-** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **x**  
E-mail address | **x** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **x**  
Phone/Fax number | **x** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **x**  
other (describe) | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
  
Primary personal data | Technical administration of the Web site | Research & development | Customer Administration | Marketing | Trading in personal data  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Employer/organisation | **-** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **-**  
Job title | **-** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **-**  
Address | **-** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **-**  
E-mail address | **-** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **-**  
Phone/Fax number | **-** | **-** | **x** | **x** | **-**  
other (describe) | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
  
#### Other personal details and profiling data

**x** | volunteered by each visitor  
---|---  
- | collected from public records or bodies  
**x** | collected from private organisations  
  
  | Technical administration of the Web site | Research & development | Customer Administration | Marketing | Trading in personal data  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Personal details | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Physical description | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Family characteristics | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Education and skills | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Life style or personal tastes | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Financial resources | **-** | **-** | **x** | **-** | **-**  
other (describe) | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
  
#### Identifiers

**x** | volunteered by each visitor  
---|---  
- | collected from public records or bodies  
**-** | collected from private organisations  
  
  | Technical administration of the Web site | Research & development | Customer Administration | Marketing | Trading in personal data  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
On-line identifiers | **x** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Financial identifiers | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Identifiers assigned by Public bodies | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Biometrics identifiers | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
other (describe) | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
  
#### Specific Data

**-** | volunteered by each visitor  
---|---  
- | collected from public records or bodies  
**-** | collected from private organisations  
  
  | Technical administration of the Web site | Research & development | Customer Administration | Marketing | Trading in personal data  
---|---|---|---|---|---  
Racial or ethnic origin | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Political opinions | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Religious or philosophical beliefs | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Trade union membership | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Health/Medical data | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Sex life | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
Police/Justice data such as civil/criminal actions brought by or against the visitor | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**  
other (describe) | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-** | **-**
